[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1, "question": "Who the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is Piers Morgan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 2, "answer": "Kid Rock is the quintessential all-American rock star.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Are you Mr. Rock?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "It doesn't really matter to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Rock"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "I mean is there a point where you'd have to change your name from Kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "And if I had 100 bucks every time somebody asked that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "You like being a rocker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I enjoy to have a good time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How wild does it get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Probably wilder than I'm willing to discuss right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Do you know how much you've consumed over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "It's what rock stars do, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I like who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Is there anything you regret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "You'd say nothing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How do you feel about being 40?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Because I can't fight it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "At what point does it become embarrassing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, I think I'll be able to rock for a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "What's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "\"Vanity Fair\" magazine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "There's always a Justin Bieber.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "What did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "He just kind of chuckled then.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Do you think there's room for everyone in music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Yes, sure there is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "It's honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Have you ever been dishonest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, I'm sure I've been dishonest at times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Jeez, where do you want to start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Wherever you want to start.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "With flying colors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Waffle Houses"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Are you -- are you only ever violent when you've been drinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I mean I'd say that's been the stupid stuff, you know, the fights in Waffle Houses and the, you know, different things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Would you -- could I actually be in fear of a right hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "So you can control it when you're in this environment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "When do you feel it descending?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "But you don't regret smacking Tommy Lee, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tommy Lee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "He deserved it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Waffle House guy, does he deserve what came his way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Waffle House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "How old is he now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Seventeen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "How have you been different as a father, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, I never really paddled him that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "I mean you've never smacked your son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No, he got a -- he got a few.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Nothing -- nothing like you got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "ID ROCK: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "But what kind of dad do you think you've been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I think I've been a good dad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "What do you think the law of the land should be for your son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Show respect to the people around you, especially have a little respect for as much as I'm gone -- and I've tried to adjust my schedule to be home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Malibu High School"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "If he started taking drugs or stuff, would you be censorious about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, you know, he actually attended Malibu High School for like one month.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "What does it mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "It's where I'm from.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 315, "question": "When you sing about Detroit, what's going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "You know --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Detroit"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "How often do you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "As often as I can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Detroit"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "And where is it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I mean, when it really started hitting -- you know, Detroit has been devastated for a lot of years and it's been going that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "You couldn't do a LeBron and -- and switch allegiance to another city?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "You can't be bought, can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "And money brings you that power, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It kind of does, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Or do you feel you put enough back into that city?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "No, it's a weird thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1930"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Cadillac"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What's the most extravagant thing you've ever bought?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I think a -- an original 1930 Cadillac.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "How much was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "It was just under a half a million dollars.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Are you a traditional Republican?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "You're more for your country than you are for a party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I think I'm -- I'm -- I think I'm like the majority of people who are tired of the -- wouldn't want a bunch of bible thumpers running the country and we don't want a bunch of pot smoking hippies running it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Do you -- do you think the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq have been just wars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "You know, that's tough to say, because, you know, it's -- when you get into politics, I know -- I know this much, I don't study political science and I didn't do that well in school.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "I mean are we -- are we winning these wars, from what you've seen on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, we -- we need to have a presence there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "And it's difficult, I think, if you look at it, you know, are we winning, do you think, from what you've seen there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "When you're on a plane with human remains and there's an American flag draped over a casket you're flying with, you know, it really sparks up some things and really makes you think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Still, when you do, what do you think the perception of your country is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Misunderstood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "And what -- what does being an American mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I think the freedom to do whatever you want, you know, with -- without taking advantage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Baby Boomers"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "And do you feel that the American dream is still what it used to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I don't know, sometimes I shake a finger at those Baby Boomers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What, do you live in a cave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I've -- I have actually interviewed --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Because she's a crazy, crazy chick, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I'm not going to get into it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Well, who are you going to argue about that with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "You.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Am I right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I'm not taking the bait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "You learned lessons, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I've learned lessons all through life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Is there anyone special in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Do you care to elaborate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Do you think that's in your makeup?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Yes, I think that's always been in my makeup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Rock"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "-- I mean it's just outrageous, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Chris Rock said that years ago in his comedy vignettes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "No, I mean you got lucky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Just totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Has it -- has it been all you hoped it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "And do you like being famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "How much have you made?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "A lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Do you know how much you make?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "None of your business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "How rich you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "I -- I guess you could say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Is it the best you've done, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "I think so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Are you an emotional guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "When was the last time you cried?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "When I found out my dad had a heart attack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "What -- what does that tell you when that sort of thing happens to you in life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Whether you care about somebody, you care about your family deeply.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "If you knew you were going to die tomorrow, what would be the one thing you'd like to relive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Jeez, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "How important to you is your credibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "It depends to who.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "What's the principal at stake here for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Well, it's very deep and it's very honest and I'm going to be very candid with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Is that your lighter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kensington"]}, "docId": "110310pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "What's your pub called?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "The Handsome Pad in Kensington.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]